Hello and welcome!
How about some piping hot fried chicken?
If you don't mind, please tap your phone there.
Here you are, sir!
Go ahead and take your lottery ticket for the campaign we're running!
Draw one, please!
By any chance...
Were you pestering me so hard yesterday just to get me to do this?
Hey, why not? It's on your way home anyway, right?
Besides, you buy your dinner at convenience stores every day!
Yeah, that's true.
I haven't seen you since the festival. How's Runa been doing?
Yeah, she seems to be studying hard.
Is that right?
She calls me every once in a while, but we hardly ever get to see each other.
Oh my, he a friend of yours, Akane?
Miss Shinohara!
He's quite a looker.
Yeah, he really is. We met playing the same game.
His face was so gorgeous!
He could be an actor.
My heart's pounding!
Okay, I'll be heading.
My shift will be over soon, so wait for me, okay?
Let's go home together!
Oh, look at him waiting so faithfully.
Are you two dating as well?
Oh, no, we're not.
He seems to have a hard time dealing with women, so it's not like that.
Well, that is a crying shame.
But that doesn't stop you from liking him now, does it?
You were so determined to keep him from leaving.
Yeah, well, I don't know about that.
Amazing! Spoken exactly like a true maiden.
I guess it is true that, compared to when we first met each other, Yamada seems to be a lot more willing to open up to me.
From the time we've spent together, I can see that he's actually a really sweet guy.
Eh, good work today.
The thought does cross my mind.
Thanks for waiting!
Even if we're only linked by a game, I still find happiness in the fact that we're able to get closer.
But now that I think about it, the same goes for Eita and Runa too, doesn't it?
You know, I didn't ask you to visit me for the lottery.
Actually, I wanted to give you this bento box I made for you, as a way of saying thank you.
For what?
My computer.
Since I couldn't really do much for you during the festival.
It's really not that big of a deal.
Now that my penny-pinching days are over for the time being, there's a pretty lavish feast in there.
For some reason, I can't shake this feeling.
Like, I shouldn't see him in a romantic light.
But I'm not sure why.
Uh-oh, I sneezed in front of someone who was about to take entrance exams.
Are you sick?
Uh, I'm not sure.
Did I have a mask in here?
You find one?
Uh-huh.
I hope that it doesn't get any worse.
You're cold?
Yeah.
Thank you.
A guy who's super kind without realizing it.
Isn't that pretty terrifying?
Keep going.
You let your guard down for one second, and it's like...
Wait, is he actually into me?
But it's just a delusion, and that's not the guy's intention at all.
He's just being kind like any decent person.
It's a terrifying trap.
Before you move on, there's one thing I want to confirm.
How can you be so sure that it's not his intention?
Also, can I try something a little flashy on you?
The theme's night, Butterfly.
Huh?
Please don't.
I'll get in trouble at work.
You haven't said any names yet.
But we're talking about Yamada here, right?
Yep.
But you were so thrilled that he said you were out of his league.
Honestly, I don't even think he meant much by that.
Hmm?
That's one of the things that makes it so terrifying.
Hmm.
All I know is that if a hot younger guy ever said that to me, even if he wasn't thinking
straight, I wouldn't waste any time making a move.
I have no idea why you're hemming and hawing about this.
I'm not hemming and hawing, Momo.
Oh, really now?
Because from where I'm sitting, it looks like the most hemming and hawing you've ever done.
I see how you light up when you're talking about Yamada, and you clearly have fun trying
to figure him out.
But this whole time, I haven't heard you say a word about what you want to do, Akane.
And you need to figure that out.
Because until you do, I can't really speak on it.
Hmm.
You're absolutely right.
Night Butterfly?
That I decline.
Oh, it's Runa.
Oh, that girl?
I remember.
The goth lolly middle schooler.
That's right.
Hi.
Akane!
Can we meet up right now?
The guild is facing a crisis!
Huh?
I'm here, Runa.
Thanks for waiting!
Are you sure it's okay for you to be out at this hour?
It's gonna get dark pretty soon.
I came by taxi, so I'm totally fine.
I'm going home by taxi, too.
Then I guess there's no worries.
Hey, listen.
This afternoon, I was with Yamada and-
Never mind that!
Did you read my text?
Yeah, sure.
I read it.
The guild's gonna be getting a new member.
A new guild member?
And yet another woman that I've never met before?
It's unbelievable.
When we started this game, we agreed to keep it in the family.
Oh, I do like you now, Akane.
But at this rate-
Sounds a bit clickish.
...my exams, it'll be a totally different guild!
And if that wasn't enough, the fact that it's a woman makes it even worse,
because women always find reasons to hate me!
Well, I'm sort of looking forward to it, you know?
Personally, I hope it's a girl who's new to online games like me.
Oh, hey!
I brought some hot chocolate.
You want some-?
Smoke it!
Anyway, I've drawn up a plan to drive the interloper out immediately.
Hey!
Players who are new have their own anxieties,
so it's on us to give them a warm welcome, okay?
And you know what?
Once you get to really know her, you might even end up as friends.
Kind of like what happened with us, Runa.
Doesn't the thought of becoming friends with someone
you normally wouldn't cross paths with sound cool?
I mean, doesn't it excite you?
L-l-not at all!
I already know that you're going to get along with her right away, Akane!
Then you're going to start hanging out with her all the time and not me!
No, silly, that's not true.
I haven't even said anything to me.
It's definitely gonna happen!
There's nothing stopping all three of us from being friends, is there?
I don't like odd numbers!
One of us will be left out!
Uh, let's all get along together, okay?
Okay?
It's like I have a jealous girlfriend now.
Yeah, well, I'm not surprised.
I knew that you'd say something like that.
And my brother's like,
This new girl is one of Yamada's important friends.
So you better be respectful and welcome her nicely.
Yamada's friend?
She's a girl in his class.
According to what I overheard,
FPS games are usually more her style.
But she wants to take a break and play an MMO.
From what I can tell, they're pretty close.
But when I called him to ask about her...
Tell me!
She's normal.
Yamada played it cool and wouldn't spill any of the beans.
And he said that if I was mean to her like when you joined,
he would get really mad at me.
So it's a girl that he's friends with.
Kind of unexpected, huh?
For Yamada to bring a girl into the guild.
Huh?
Yeah, I guess so.
Ugh!
Never mind that!
Runa has a great idea!
Give me your phone!
Hm?
What are you doing?
I'm saving Yamada's number for you.
That way you can call him Akane!
He was being cautious when I asked about her,
but I bet he'd be willing to open up to you.
If I just knew what she's like,
then Runa could rest easy.
And apparently they just started dating after that.
For real?
But didn't they claim that they weren't each other's type?
Well, yeah, but still.
You know how it is.
Even if you think there's no way it could happen,
two people can always end up together over something trivial.
Is it really possible
for people to fall in love over something trivial?
Yo, Prez, how goes it?
Good evening, Okamoto and Yamada.
Hello.
So anyway, Prez,
it was pretty funny how you came walking in here
muttering to yourself.
But I was directing the question at you two.
About lovers, huh?
The thing is,
I'm not so sure we're the right people to ask about that subject.
Yeah, good point.
By the way, Yamada,
thank you for helping me get into your guild
and talking to the guild master for me.
Sure.
What's this about?
A game I play.
Oh, Foss, huh?
I just started playing it myself,
and I heard that it's better to be in one of the stronger guilds.
So I asked Yamada to let me be a member of his.
Well, Prez, you are a secret gamer, ain't you?
I wouldn't say that I'm hiding it or anything,
but it's not like I can talk about it casually with the other girls.
They just talk about boys.
No way!
Does that mean you talk about boys with them, too?
Not really.
I see.
So you've sacrificed your precious youth to gaming, too, huh?
Not answering?
It's an unknown number,
and class is about to start anyway.
It stopped.
You seem to get a lot of random calls like that,
don't you, Yamada?
And when you do pick up,
it's usually some girl confessing her love to you.
If you wanted to, you could get any...
Leave Yamada alone.
Romance isn't his thing.
Isn't that right?
Well, no, I guess not.
I thought so.
I'm so hungry!
If I don't eat soon, I'll die.
Didn't you just have a hamburger before class started?
Man, I'd kill for another burger.
Again?
Man, I want some fries to go with it, too.
Hey, are you listening?
One sec.
Ooh, calling that person from earlier?
If it's a girl with a sweet voice,
pass the phone over to me, okay?
Don't ignore me.
Coming!
Yes?
I'm sorry.
You just called me.
Yamada?
It's me, Akane.
Akane?
I knew it was a girl.
Hold on.
Huh?
Did I give you my...
I know, I know.
Sorry for the random call.
The thing is, I was hanging out with Runa this evening.
Are you all right?
Yeah, sure.
Anyway, I called earlier to ask you something,
but I can't talk now because I have to go to work.
Didn't you work this afternoon?
Well, my boss couldn't get a hold of the person
who's supposed to be on night shift,
so I got called in on short notice again.
Isn't there anyone who can switch with you?
No, no one seems free.
Since I live so close by,
I guess that makes me fair game.
So that's so.
Hey, Yamada?
Yes?
Your voice is a little lower over the phone.
Never mind.
That person who called you,
was it the girl from the festival?
Yes, it was.
How'd you know?
Because I heard you say her name.
We're in the same guild in Foss,
so you'll be hanging out with her too,
sooner or later.
I see.
Even in private,
you seem pretty close.
I guess so.
The guildmaster was an upperclassman back home.
I can't remember her face.
What's she like?
Huh?
A...
You mean the master?
Mm-mm.
The person named Akane.
Akane is...
Uh...
This handsome fella is my boyfriend!
We didn't have a one-night stand, did we?
Yamada!
I couldn't say.
Could it be that?
You like her?
Akane!
Sorry to make you come in.
I really owe you one.
I can't get in touch with the night shift worker,
and there's no way that I can handle it on my own.
I'm so sick of this habitual shirker.
Don't you think it's high time you get them fired?
Uh, well, yeah, I suppose you're right.
But he's not all bad, you know?
He really loves guitars.
But hey, I'll pay you back with a nice dinner.
Does tomorrow night work well for you?
I know a great place!
Not going!
Ah!
I wanted to sleep early because I'm coming down with a cold.
Seems strange to have Yamada's name in my call history.
All right.
Let's get to work.
But this whole time, I haven't heard you say a word about what you want to do, Akane.
Akane!
Ah!
Coming!
Not good.
Let's go.
Not that I still have feelings for him, but now, maybe just a little.
Sorry, Akane.
I do have some regrets.
It's Akane!
Can I take this?
Sure thing.
Hey, Akane, what's up?
Runa's in a tutoring session right now.
Runa...
Why does your voice sound like that?
A cold?
Then does that mean you can't play with me tonight?
Oh, I see.
No, no, that's okay.
It can't be helped, right?
I hope you feel better.
Akane says she came down with a cold.
It sounded like she was dying.
I wonder if she'll be okay.
I hope it's nothing too serious.
Oh, my goodness.
my throat hurts so much i can't drink any water i've got to take some medicine
actually before that i need to eat something i haven't eaten since yesterday
i'ma lay down for a sec
i'm exhausted and somehow i picked the perfect time to run completely out of luck
this sucks but still no one's gonna show up and help me even if i weep and wail
so unless i take action only death awaits me
first i gotta eat maybe something like rice gruel but i'm out of rice gotta go shopping
can't take the bus or i'll spread my germs i'll just ride my bike
yeah good girl your brain is still working
i don't know how but i've got to will myself to get through tonight
what am i thinking there's no way i can ride a bike
so hot wait can i get something delivered why didn't i think of that
i take out should do smart girl but first i need to put these bikes back
and after i'm done i'll head back to my apartment
then what am i supposed to do
my head hurts
Akane
what's going on i can see someone who looks like yamada
but there's no way he'd be at my place right
can you hear me
a dream oh come on
now he's even showing up in my dreams
i'm sorry yamada for having such a self-serving dream
Butterfly, Butterfly, come shine your light on me!
Night, Butterfly, Momoko Maeda. Tonight, I'm finally going to capture my prince-
AHHHHH!
Excuse me, I'd like another, with extra gin!
Momo's not picking up, I guess.
AHHHHH!